I walked
year
Once a
meet
curtain to
behind a
God
sure
never
and I was
back out.
walk
I would
gave me two
law
The
for one sin.
goats
and
first
I killed the
the
inside
blood
carried its
veil.
I did not
second
The
kill
hands on
my
I laid
head,
its
sin of the
every
confessed
it,
over
people
it into the
drove
and
to be lost.
desert
to pay.
One
away.
it
One to carry
I asked why
years
For
two.
it took
now.
know
I
could hold
creature
No single
halves.
both
Man
a
Long after me
did what my
Jesus
named
only pictured
goats
two
paid,
price
He was the
the guilt
One
and the
on:
laid
was
hath laid
LORD
and the
of
iniquity
on him the
all.
us
Himself
away
He carried it
down.
sat
once and
Finished.
behind
trembled
The curtain I
hour
in two the
tore
died.
He
sign.
I was only the
substance.
He is the
come to me,
Don't
goat,
or a
altar.
or an
Jesus
Come to
in is torn
way
the
open.
wide
in.
Walk